<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<databaseChangeLog
        xmlns="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog"
        xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
        xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog
                      http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/dbchangelog-2.0.xsd">

    <changeSet author="Alejandro" id="210120211358-changelog">
        <insert tableName="book">
            <column name="id" valueNumeric="1"></column>
            <column name="author" value="Miguel de Cervantes"></column>
            <column name="title" value="Don Quixote"></column>
            <column name="overview" value="Alonso Quixano, a retired country gentleman in his fifties, lives in an unnamed section of La Mancha with his niece and a housekeeper.
He has become obsessed with books of chivalry, and believes their every word to be true, despite the fact that many of the events in them are clearly impossible.
Quixano eventually appears to other people to have lost his mind from little sleep and food and because of so much reading. "></column>
            <column name="pages" valueNumeric="863"></column>
        </insert>
        <insert tableName="book">
            <column name="id" valueNumeric="2"></column>
            <column name="author" value="J. K. Rowling"></column>
            <column name="title" value="Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire"></column>
            <column name="overview" value="Lord Voldemort, the dark wizard responsible for the deaths of Harry's parents,
is growing stronger. At the Quidditch World Cup, Voldemort's signature Dark Mark appears in the sky over the stadium, causing pandemonium.
The lightning-bolt-shaped scar on Harry's forehead is sporadically causing him agonizing pain,
and he is also hearing disturbing voices. Harry realizes that all this is the result of a strong connection between himself and the Dark Lord, one that is putting him in grave danger.
Back at Hogwarts, the students are getting ready for the upcoming Triwizard Tournament. Witches and wizards from two other schools are coming to Hogwarts for the year to compete in a series of grueling contests.
The tournament is open only to students age 17 and above, but when someone secretly enters Harry's name, he is forced to compete.
How can a 14-year-old possibly pass tests that might be fatal to an advanced wizard? And with the threat of Lord Voldemort looming,
will he be able to focus on the tournament at all? For Harry, his friends, and everyone in the Wizarding world,
the stakes are about to become much higher. This fourth installment, with a heart-pounding and emotional climax,
serves as a turning point in the series, for the reader and for Harry himself."></column>
            <column name="pages" valueNumeric="636"></column>
        </insert>
    </changeSet>
</databaseChangeLog>